Guide to the
Brown University Library
- JJ_Reading.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Readings, Tarot Etc/Date created: 2010-08-28 23:01:01 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-30 14:05:25 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 7 Get Ready To Do Your Gender/Date created: 2012-05-29 10:22:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-29 13:37:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 04 Just Say No.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 16:47:38 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 16:47:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Chelsea Manning Open Letter/Date created: 2013-08-24 18:59:33 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-24 21:34:23 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Crossed Genres Interview.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Crossed Genres/Date created: 2010-08-30 17:53:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-30 17:53:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- cover sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-04-08 17:06:18 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-08 17:12:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB Edits Summary MNGW 2nd Proofs.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Design Round 3/Date created: 2013-03-02 17:28:54 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-03-02 18:45:22 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- how the sea org made a man out of me.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 2 Chap 5/how the sea org made a man out of me ƒ/Date created: 2008-09-08 20:39:19 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-01-17 12:58:50 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB_on_Hate_Crimes_Bill_4PHB.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Crap Drafts and Might As Well Be/Date created: 2009-11-03 11:55:00 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-04 22:40:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- best wishes for laura ingraham.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Date created: 2012-01-14 13:55:35 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-14 13:55:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- New Safer Sex section—KB PASS.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2017-04-05 19:55:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-05 19:55:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Orgasms with Spirit Class #4 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/6/7/1/Attachments/176212/1/Date created: 2015-10-22 19:56:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-22 19:56:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Letter to Oxford re Deductible Year.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Date created: 2010-12-15 14:06:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-12-15 17:39:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Quotes About KB.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate B 4U/Blurbs & Bios/Date created: 2013-07-21 23:22:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-07-23 21:04:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Rainbow w Unicorn.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-23 17:58:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-23 17:59:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW TOC and Intro.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 0 TOC and Intro/Date created: 2012-07-06 13:02:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-08 14:29:41 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 1 clean.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-24 13:44:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-24 15:05:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS-3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Taxes/KB 2009 Taxes/Date created: 2010-08-31 13:54:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-31 14:52:07 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 1st QPD Press Release.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Date created: 2012-01-14 11:01:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-14 11:01:31 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Taxes/KB 2009 Taxes/Date created: 2010-08-31 13:00:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-31 14:52:23 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW BW w ruby slippers.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-24 10:54:02 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-24 11:01:35 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- catalogue essay 13-14.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Newsletters/2013-2014 Catalogue/Date created: 2013-01-29 12:23:26 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-29 15:49:05 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- dvd case insert lana and kar.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Futa for Lana and Kar/Date created: 2009-09-03 17:08:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-03 19:00:43 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Femme Conf Keynote/Date created: 2010-08-20 15:26:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-20 15:26:25 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB CBST Pride Shabat 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2012-06-23 08:31:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-24 21:17:01 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Carrol Univ Coming Out Day.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/political pieces/Coming Out Day/Date created: 2010-10-19 21:55:30 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-19 21:55:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Text for Cover Proposal 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Layout & Design/Date created: 2011-06-27 00:02:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-27 10:58:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Blurb Letter Janet Reitman copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2011-09-27 20:38:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-28 13:22:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB pass at TCKB.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2012-01-10 18:08:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-11 00:23:56 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein_iphonecontract.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Hello Cruel World/Date created: 2010-06-28 14:25:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-06-28 14:25:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Bornstein workshop contract.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Vancouver Queer Arts Festival 2012/Date created: 2012-07-10 14:49:55 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-10 14:50:56 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KATE BORNSTEIN schedule.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/WSU Pullman WA/Date created: 2010-08-31 21:41:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-31 21:41:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Circumstances by Design.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 19:28:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 19:30:58 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 8 Do Your Gender Mindfully/Date created: 2012-06-21 13:05:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-04 22:42:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie—Gold.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Cleanest, Newest/Date created: 2011-09-06 12:27:26 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-06 12:32:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Limericks.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-03-17 14:39:36 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-28 19:26:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Open Letter re Marriage Equality.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Date created: 2009-12-04 18:48:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-09 11:54:32 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- NEW PATIENT QUESTIONNARIE2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/Block Center/Date created: 2013-02-21 23:14:09 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-03-03 17:53:30 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Hard Candy Chapter 3 Reader.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Storage/next/Hard Candy ƒ/activating candy/Hard Candy: da book/Date created: 2010-09-09 17:40:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-09-09 20:20:08 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/BC Ecstasy Is Neccessary/Date created: 2012-02-28 15:27:40 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-28 15:27:40 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Tao of Mitzvah Etc for RRC 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2012-03-12 23:04:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-03-12 23:04:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1 Beta_EW.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-05-15 11:51:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-15 14:13:59 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- On Men, Women and The Rest of Us AV.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2009-03-28 10:53:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-28 12:00:36 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- *GSMS Foreword by BC—KB pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2011-12-22 21:23:51 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-12-22 21:24:11 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kate's itinerary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/Tacoma/Date created: 2009-04-22 22:28:26 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-04-22 22:28:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Urban Tantra certificate.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2009-11-29 13:18:39 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-29 14:42:30 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- There and Back Again.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/4/8/1/Attachments/184657/1/Date created: 2015-10-23 12:04:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-23 12:04:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Author Questionnaire by Kate Bornstein.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Bios-KB/Author Questionnaires/Date created: 2012-05-26 11:35:08 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-26 11:35:08 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 4.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 4 Let Why = Why/Date created: 2012-02-16 12:47:47 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-03-05 17:37:51 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ltr to Beth Israel Pathology.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2012-11-19 13:56:52 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-11-19 13:56:52 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 06 The Playgrounds.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 16:57:26 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 16:57:26 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MWRU Performance Script 2016 PO9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Performance Scripts/Script Attic/Date created: 2017-03-04 13:39:38 EST-0500Date modified: 2017-03-04 13:39:38 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Epilogue/Early Epilogue/Date created: 2011-09-05 12:36:17 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-05 17:29:31 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Jan 2012.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2012-01-12 12:33:51 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-12 12:35:21 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~~Copy Editing QPD~~/Date created: 2011-10-18 12:28:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-26 13:59:28 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 Where It Gets Complicated V2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated/Date created: 2011-06-15 18:23:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-21 19:15:42 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Orgasms with Spirit Class #4 KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2013-08-07 10:48:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-07 11:07:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Apartheid of Sex Martine Rothblatt.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Date created: 2011-05-17 23:18:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-17 23:18:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Genesis Pomo.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Tao of Sabbath Mitvah Boddhisatva ƒ/Date created: 2012-03-12 23:00:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-03-12 23:00:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- copy_txt.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Hello Cruel World/Date created: 2010-02-24 21:22:34 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-24 21:22:34 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- rainbow back cover beta 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-09-04 13:09:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-09-04 13:11:56 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Affirmations for Docs.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2008-06-12 01:18:26 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-06-07 16:35:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- text to grab 4 New York the First Time.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/ Book 2, Chapter 4/New York, the First Time ƒ/Date created: 2009-01-17 12:59:58 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-02-03 16:14:00 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- short talk performance & workshop descriptions.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/blurbs bios pix/Date created: 2013-09-02 18:20:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-02 18:20:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft_BC pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail Downloads/Date created: 2012-02-29 10:52:33 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-29 11:18:51 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MWRU Script La Mama 2017 BC copy.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/57F6CF73-8A8B-4A58-8154-FFD84FE00244/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/9/6/3/Attachments/369988/1/Date created: 2017-04-15 16:57:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-15 16:57:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum for blog.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Keynote Women Gender Studies Consortium/Date created: 2009-11-08 00:31:35 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-08 00:31:35 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- william paterson piece.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Beyond Red or Blue/Date created: 2008-09-22 10:50:54 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-02-28 14:33:56 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-1 Beta 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3 Chapter 1/Date created: 2010-07-02 13:57:28 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-07-03 15:10:02 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- KB workshop promo .pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/8D5A1E6A-3871-48CC-B85B-B014FE3DEA28/Tour Venues Booked.mbox/Been There, Done That.mbox/UK Tour Feb 2016.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/3/8/2/Attachments/283080/2/Date created: 2016-01-05 13:02:24 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-05 13:02:24 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Brown Piece.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Itty Bitty Archive/Brown Anthology/Date created: 2013-05-04 14:43:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-05-05 14:50:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 05 Just Say Yes, Zen & Art of Gender Maintenance.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Workbook Attic/My New Gender Workbook Working by Chapter/Date created: 2012-01-03 16:55:27 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-03 16:55:27 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A.Mc.Q.201120.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/kaylynn/Date created: 2010-02-13 22:58:08 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-02-13 22:58:08 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Author 1st proof AQs (Chap 3 to End).pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/2nd Proofs Go/Date created: 2013-02-01 11:55:02 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-02-01 13:18:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Midnight Bleary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/caitlin/Date created: 2010-01-15 17:15:02 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-15 17:15:07 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Cautionary Interlude.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-06-28 11:58:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-28 11:58:53 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Sleeping Beauty.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/Sleeping Beauty/Date created: 2010-04-20 14:47:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-20 18:08:34 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 1 Gender Aptitude/Date created: 2012-02-04 17:42:35 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-02-09 13:47:21 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QueerPleasantDanger_1_5_illustrated.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/scripts/Queer&Pleasant Solo Show/Queer & Pleasant Illustrated/Date created: 2010-01-03 11:40:26 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-01-04 11:02:33 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages